internetfreedom.org 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Global Internet Freedom Consortium

GIF Privacy Policy

This document was last updated on January 1, 2010.

1\. Acknowledgment and acceptance of terms

Global Internet Freedom Consortium (“GIF”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you use GIF’s official anti-censorship services and their associated software products (“GIF Services”).  By using GIF Services, you acknowledge and fully understand GIF’s Privacy Policy and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy.

2\. Information We Collect

Personal information: GIF does not collect or require users of GIF Services to furnish personal information, including name, phone number, credit card number and physical address that can be used to identify a user. GIF will collect your email address or instant messaging service account name and the content of your communication when you choose to contact GIF via these means. 

Non-personal information: GIF collects information that includes but is not limited to your computer’s configuration and the version of the software for GIF Services. GIF will also collect network traffic data for the debugging session when you choose to report debugging information to GIF. 

Potentially personal information: GIF collects the type and version of your web browser and computer operating system, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses, Uniform Resource Locators (“URLs”) you visit with GIF Services, date and time of these visits, and their referring URLs. 

3\. Information We Send to Websites

GIF Services relays the information between you and the websites you visit, except your IP addresses, which will be replaced with GIF’s own IP addresses.  Each website has its own privacy policy for the collection and use of your information. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of the websites you visit before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such websites.

  4\. How We Use Your Information

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

  * To protect ourselves from liability, 
  * To respond to legal process or comply with law, or 
  * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company. 

GIF reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies.

5\. Changes to this Policy

GIF has the discretion to occasionally update this Privacy Policy.  When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page.  We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.  Your continued use of GIF Services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

6\. Contacting Us

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Policy and/or our general practices, please contact us or send your comments to: contact@internetfreedom.org.
